Hello, hello friend, I am Bina Nirbhik friend,
welcome once again friends,
as you all know that right now you all are
waiting for the IBPS Clerk result
and today the budget is going on, you should like to see,
okay, let me tell you when, what and how is happening, the
budget is being released today, you all are keeping an eye on it
and from there you got the news,
friends, you want bad news, bad
news for banking, insurance sector and
experience, that is, the center is going bankrupt, the guys
who prepare for
banking and insurance will also go, okay, now you all are right now
waiting for the IBPS Clerk result,
okay, now see what can happen in that too, a
lot can happen, I will make a video from it, I will
tell you what will be its rate, I will
tell you about its result, but right now the
face news is coming that two PSBs, okay, those
two public sector banks and one which is
an insurance company, these three will be
privatized, now think, right now
some people will spread the knowledge that there is a
difference between prioritization and disinvestment, so friends, by doing
disinvestment, these people IDBI, practice the
whole method  It will happen in future as well,
tell me, we reached 22,
then we will bring it down to five, the time is with you, if we
leave then people will add, so see
how many slice banks are left, it seems except this, no
one will be left, okay, SBI
can increase the bank,
PNB can increase it, these three banks are visible which
can be saved, okay, the government can keep some power in its hands,
those banks which do not have everything,
whatever is their condition, but right now the rest of the union
operations will eliminate any disease completely,
okay friends, so this is the only
news channel for you people, now I will
say this only that if you people leave the banking sector, it will be
better,
focus only on Aloe Vera, there is nothing left here,
now how am I saying this, I myself am not able to
understand, I do not feel like saying it,
just understand this, now banking will be completely
finished, nothing will be left now, Railways should be finished,
Radha, there is a deep objection there also,
now see what happens next, okay,
I am not going to say anything more than this,
thank you friends